Well, hey, let's have a fun conversation about the Supreme Court and I'll just go ahead and
preface this with, if what I'm about to say pisses you off, you should hang around because
I have something you can do with that anger by the end. They got rid of Roe v. Wade tossing out
decades of legal precedent and it has literally made multiple states a hellscape for women who
are now being labeled criminals for seeking health care. They ruled in favor of that woman
who said she didn't want to design a website for a same-sex couple's wedding and then it turned out
that that entire thing was a sham. There was no same-sex couple that had tried to hire her.
One of the guys didn't exist. The other guy was straight and married and lived in a different
state from her and had never seen her before and wasn't trying to marry a dude. And oh, by the way,
if he needed a website for his wedding, he was a web designer and they fell for it, hook, line,
and sinker, and now created a dangerous precedent for same-sex couples. Oh, and let's not forget
that the arguments made to get rid of Roe v. Wade could also be made about the protections for
same-sex marriage and for interracial couples. And I know you hear that and you go, look, the
Supreme Court's not going to say it's illegal for two different races to get married. They don't have
to. They just have to say it's up to the individual state. And then I promise you, there is a Republican
somewhere who'll be like, this is a way to get my name in the papers. Oh, and don't forget Justice
Thomas having gifts and trips and tuition for his kids paid for by his billionaire buddy.
You know how valuable it is to have a Supreme Court justice in your pocket? Not to mention,
he actually heard cases that came before the court that would affect his friend, the outcome of those
cases, and did not recuse himself. Thought, still okay. And I say all this because today is a special
day. It is the 18-year anniversary of Judge Samuel Alito being sworn in as a Supreme Court justice.
He has been a Supreme Court justice for 18 years, and I feel like we should get him something.
I found the perfect gift that you can give him as well. And that gift is called term limits.
Because if you were to sign this petition, Lincoln Bio, it says that you support legislation that's
currently in front of Congress, that if they pass, says that after 18 years, a justice has to step
down. Oh, look at that. That would mean that this would be Justice Alito's last year. He'd be all
done. And someone else would be taking his place. That sounds pretty good. You know, I saw this and I
told him, I'm going to put this up as a gift to Justice Alito. And they were like, yeah, how many
gifts do you think you can give him? And I was like, how many you want? They said, you think you need
5,000 signatures? I said, bet. So do me a favor, go to the link, take 30 seconds to sign this.
Because there's no reason that people should be serving on the highest court in the land
while they're quite literally on their deathbed. 18 years is plenty. Let's get some term limits going,
shall we?